An	O
application	O
integration	O
system	O
originally	O
from	O
Active	O
Software	O
Inc	O
that	O
runs	O
on	O
Solaris	B-ORG
,	O
HP/UX	B-ORG
,	O
Windows	B-MISC
and	I-MISC
IRIX	B-ORG

An	O
umbrella	O
term	O
for	O
capturing	O
data	O
about	O
a	O
person	O
or	O
object	O
electronically	O

An	O
optical	O
disc	O
technology	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
creation	O
of	O
the	O
bit	O
permanently	O
alters	O
the	O
recording	O
material	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
data	O
cannot	O
be	O
changed	O

An	O
advertising	O
effort	O
that	O
places	O
ads	O
on	O
a	O
Web	O
page	O
or	O
application	O
via	O
the	O
Internet	B-MISC

An	O
English-like	O
command	O
language	O
for	O
the	O
Macintosh	O
introduced	O
with	O
System	O
7	O
Pro	O
and	O
supported	O
in	O
Mac	B-ORG
OS	I-ORG
X	I-ORG
,	O
even	O
though	O
OS	B-ORG
X	O
has	O
its	O
own	O
Unix	O
commands	O

An	O
additional	O
power	O
source	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
event	O
of	O
power	O
failure	O

An	O
initiative	O
from	O
Maxtor	B-ORG
,	O
Compaq	B-ORG
,	O
Microsoft	B-ORG
and	O
others	O
to	O
increase	O
the	O
maximum	O
capacity	O
of	O
ATA	B-ORG
drives	O
from	O
137GB	O
to	O
144PB	O
by	O
upgrading	O
the	O
address	O
size	O
to	O
48	O
bits	O

An	O
earlier	O
Nortel	B-ORG
Networks	I-ORG
brand	O
name	O
for	O
its	O
Ethernet	O
switches	O
and	O
hubs	O

An	O
entity	O
bean	O
that	O
is	O
responsible	O
for	O
its	O
own	O
storage	O
,	O
typically	O
through	O
JDBC	B-ORG
code	O
in	O
its	O
methods	O

An	O
integrated	O
circuit	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
cut	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
wafer	O
and	O
is	O
ready	O
for	O
packaging	O

An	O
early	O
family	O
of	O
computers	O
from	O
Control	B-ORG
Data	I-ORG
that	O
ranged	O
from	O
workstations	O
to	O
supercomputers	O

An	O
off-the-shelf	O
device	O
that	O
is	O
readily	O
available	O
for	O
purchase	O

An	O
integrated	O
information	O
system	O
that	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
plan	O
,	O
schedule	O
and	O
control	O
the	O
presales	O
and	O
postsales	O
activities	O
in	O
an	O
organization	O

An	O
IETF	B-ORG
standard	O
for	O
exchanging	O
policy	O
information	O
in	O
a	O
network	O

An	O
electronic	O
astronaut	O

An	O
earlier	O
application	O
development	O
system	O
for	O
Windows	B-MISC
and	I-MISC
OS/2	O
from	O
CA	B-ORG
Technologies	I-ORG

An	O
application	O
development	O
system	O
from	O
CA	B-ORG
Technologies	I-ORG
for	O
IBM	B-ORG
mainframes	O
and	O
Unix	O

An	O
increase	O
in	O
size	O
of	O
each	O
dot	O
of	O
ink	O
when	O
printed	O
due	O
to	O
temperature	O
,	O
ink	O
and	O
paper	O
type	O

An	O
application	O
that	O
allows	O
for	O
the	O
creation	O
and	O
management	O
of	O
information	O
and	O
ads	O
on	O
digital	O
signs	O

An	O
earlier	O
full-featured	O
IBM	B-ORG
word	O
processing	O
program	O
for	O
PCs	O
that	O
stemmed	O
from	O
the	O
typewriter-oriented	O
DisplayWriter	O
word	O
processing	O
system	O
first	O
introduced	O
in	O
1980	O

An	O
Internet-based	B-MISC
global	O
communications	O
network	O
created	O
by	O
the	O
U	B-ORG

An	O
organization	O
that	O
sets	O
up	O
and	O
manages	O
PKI	O
systems	O
for	O
companies	O
and	O
industry	O
groups	O

An	O
electromechanical	O
device	O
that	O
contains	O
and	O
reads	O
and	O
writes	O
magnetic	O
disks	O
,	O
optical	O
discs	O
or	O
magnetic	O
tapes	O

An	O
illegal	O
change	O
to	O
a	O
DNS	O
server	O
that	O
directs	O
a	O
URL	O
to	O
a	O
different	O
Web	O
site	O

An	O
automobile	O
that	O
is	O
powered	O
entirely	O
or	O
partially	O
by	O
electricity	O

An	O
undocumented	O
function	O
hidden	O
in	O
software	O
that	O
may	O
or	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
sanctioned	O
by	O
management	O

An	O
e-cigarette	O
for	O
marijuana	O
,	O
available	O
at	O
medical	O
marijuana	O
dispensaries	O

An	O
arithmetic	O
expression	O
that	O
equates	O
one	O
set	O
of	O
conditions	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
for	O
example	O
,	O
A	O
=	O
B	O
+	O
C	O

An	O
application	O
development	O
system	O
for	O
enterprise	O
client/server	O
environments	O
from	O
Sun	B-ORG

An	O
Android	O
smartphone	O
from	O
Amazon.com	B-ORG

An	O
earlier	O
Windows	B-MISC
3.1	I-MISC
driver	O
that	O
speeded	O
up	O
disk	O
access	O
by	O
running	O
in	O
32-bit	O
mode	O
,	O
bypassing	O
DOS	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
BIOS	O
and	O
communicating	O
directly	O
with	O
the	O
disk	O
controller	O

An	O
RSS	B-ORG
newsreader	O
from	O
Google	B-ORG
that	O
was	O
launched	O
in	O
2005	O

An	O
earlier	O
name	O
for	O
router	O

An	O
early	O
provider	O
of	O
IP	O
voice	O
services	O
via	O
the	O
Internet	B-MISC
,	O
intranets	O
and	O
private	O
WANs	B-ORG
that	O
sold	O
its	O
customer	O
base	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
1990s	O

An	O
always-on	O
voice	O
circuit	O
between	O
two	O
or	O
more	O
parties	O

An	O
automobile	O
from	O
Hypercar	B-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
,	O
Basalt	B-LOC
,	O
CO	B-LOC
that	O
uses	O
advanced	O
concepts	O

An	O
earlier	O
,	O
popular	O
graphics	O
file	O
conversion	O
and	O
screen	O
capture	O
program	O
for	O
Windows	B-MISC
from	I-MISC
IMSI	B-LOC
,	O
Novato	B-LOC
,	O
CA	B-LOC

An	O
area	O
with	O
excessive	O
heat	O
in	O
the	O
datacenter	O

An	O
ANSI	B-ORG
file	O
format	O
that	O
is	O
system	O
independent	O
and	O
also	O
intended	O
for	O
human	O
interpretation	O

An	O
earlier	O
DVD	O
burner	O
application	O
from	O
Apple	B-ORG

An	O
earlier	O
family	O
of	O
desktop	O
graphics	O
computers	O
from	O
SGI	B-LOC

An	O
OS/2	O
feature	O
that	O
supports	O
multiple	O
file	O
systems	O

An	O
IBM	B-ORG
mainframe	O
program	O
that	O
transfers	O
files	O
between	O
the	O
mainframe	O
and	O
a	O
PC	O
functioning	O
as	O
a	O
3270	O
terminal	O

An	O
information	O
provider	O
that	O
gathers	O
content	O
from	O
several	O
sources	O
and	O
functions	O
as	O
a	O
data	O
aggregator	O
for	O
a	O
target	O
audience	O

An	O
application	O
software	O
platform	O
from	O
Oracle	O
for	O
smart	O
cards	O
based	O
on	O
a	O
subset	O
of	O
the	O
Java	B-MISC
programming	O
language	O

An	O
early	O
family	O
of	O
client/server	O
tools	O
for	O
analyzing	O
data	O
from	O
multidimensional	O
databases	O
from	O
Pilot	O
Software	O
,	O
Cambridge	B-LOC
,	O
MA	B-LOC
,	O
a	O
pioneer	O
in	O
the	O
OLAP	O
database	O
field	O

An	O
evaluation	O
of	O
the	O
print	O
quality	O
of	O
an	O
electric	O
typewriter	O
,	O
indicating	O
suitability	O
for	O
business	O
correspondence	O

An	O
electronic	O
circuit	O
that	O
performs	O
some	O
type	O
of	O
processing	O
or	O
controlling	O
function	O

An	O
IP	O
address	O
in	O
the	O
range	O
from	O
169.254.1.0	O
to	O
169.254.254.255	O

An	O
electromagnetic	O
wave	O
that	O
oscillates	O
in	O
the	O
range	O
from	O
300,000	O
to	O
3,000,000	O
Hz	O

An	O
individual	O
who	O
modifies	O
an	O
off-the-shelf	O
component	O
,	O
typically	O
a	O
PC	O

An	O
architecture	O
for	O
building	O
applications	O
that	O
separates	O
the	O
logic	O
and	O
data	O
,	O
the	O
user	O
interface	O
and	O
processing	O

An	O
enhancement	O
to	O
the	O
IP	O
protocol	O
that	O
forwards	O
e-mail	O
and	O
other	O
data	O
to	O
traveling	O
users	O

An	O
intermediate-sized	O
version	O
of	O
the	O
SD	B-LOC
memory	O
card	O

An	O
electronic	O
commerce	O
transaction	O
of	O
very	O
low	O
value	O

An	O
input/output	O
architecture	O
developed	O
by	O
Intel	B-ORG
that	O
evolved	O
into	O
InfiniBand	B-MISC

An	O
organization	O
that	O
delivers	O
telecommunications	O
services	O
over	O
a	O
typically	O
large	O
geographic	O
area	O

An	O
ANSI-standard	O
protocol	O
for	O
videotex	O
and	O
teletext	O

An	O
open	O
source	O
version	O
of	O
the	O
SSL	B-ORG
and	O
TLS	B-ORG
security	O
protocols	O

An	O
X	O
Window-based	O
graphical	O
user	O
interface	O
for	O
Unix	O
from	O
Sun	B-ORG

An	O
initiative	O
spearheaded	O
in	O
2013	O
by	O
Facebook	O
to	O
design	O
server	O
motherboards	O
that	O
accept	O
different	O
types	O
of	O
CPU	O
chips	O

An	O
application	O
that	O
is	O
available	O
over	O
the	O
Web	O
,	O
typically	O
via	O
the	O
Web	O
browser	O

An	O
earlier	O
keyboard	O
macro	O
processor	O
for	O
DOS	B-ORG
and	O
Windows	B-MISC
from	I-MISC
CE	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
,	O
West	B-LOC
Des	B-LOC
Moines	I-LOC
,	O
IA	B-LOC
that	O
allowed	O
users	O
to	O
eliminate	O
repetitive	O
typing	O
by	O
setting	O
up	O
an	O
occurrence	O
of	O
text	O
or	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
commands	O
as	O
a	O
macro	O

An	O
architecture	O
using	O
multiple	O
computers	O

An	O
early	O
IBM	B-ORG
personal	O
computer	O

An	O
earlier	O
online	O
information	O
service	O
that	O
provided	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
Internet	B-MISC
,	O
e-mail	O
and	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
databases	O

An	O
earlier	O
OEM	O
version	O
of	O
Novell	B-ORG
's	O
NetWare	B-ORG
operating	O
system	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
compiled	O
for	O
a	O
specific	O
vendor	O
's	O
machine	O

An	O
advertisement	O
that	O
is	O
automatically	O
played	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
video	O
content	O
selected	O
by	O
the	O
user	O

An	O
open	O
source	O
development	O
platform	O
from	O
Qt	B-PER
Software	I-PER
,	O
a	O
Norwegian	B-MISC
unit	O
of	O
Nokia	B-ORG

An	O
8-line	O
telephone	O
interface	O
used	O
with	O
alarm	O
systems	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
line	O
even	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
being	O
used	O

An	O
access	O
point	O
set	O
up	O
by	O
an	O
attacker	O
outside	O
a	O
facility	O
with	O
a	O
wireless	O
network	O

An	O
operating	O
state	O
of	O
a	O
Linux/Unix	O
operating	O
system	O

An	O
open	O
architecture	O
for	O
transmitting	O
voice	O
and	O
video	O
signals	O

An	O
umbrella	O
term	O
for	O
integrating	O
and	O
managing	O
multiple	O
independent	O
,	O
self-contained	O
systems	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
entity	O

An	O
Internet	B-MISC
telephone	O
and	O
video	O
calling	O
service	O
from	O
Skype	B-ORG
Technologies	I-ORG
S	O

An	O
on-screen	O
symbol	O
that	O
indicates	O
the	O
operating	O
system	O
is	O
ready	O
for	O
a	O
command	O

An	O
LCD	O
technology	O
that	O
twists	O
liquid	O
molecules	O
greater	O
than	O
90	O
degrees	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
improve	O
contrast	O
and	O
viewing	O
angle	O

An	O
individual	O
or	O
organization	O
that	O
builds	O
systems	O
from	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
diverse	O
components	O

An	O
encryption	O
method	O
that	O
uses	O
the	O
same	O
secret	O
key	O
to	O
encrypt	O
and	O
decrypt	O
messages	O

An	O
application	O
server	O
that	O
provides	O
the	O
facilities	O
for	O
running	O
Java	B-MISC
servlets	O

An	O
automobile	O
with	O
advanced	O
electronics	O

An	O
addition	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
application	O
,	O
routine	O
or	O
device	O
that	O
works	O
smoothly	O
with	O
the	O
existing	O
system	O

An	O
environment	O
that	O
is	O
created	O
for	O
testing	O
purposes	O

An	O
earlier	O
letter	O
quality	O
printer	O
similar	O
to	O
a	O
daisy	O
wheel	O
printer	O

An	O
IBM	B-ORG
circuit	O
packaging	O
technique	O
that	O
seals	O
chips	O
,	O
boards	O
and	O
components	O
into	O
a	O
module	O
that	O
serves	O
as	O
a	O
heat	O
sink	O

An	O
activity	O
or	O
request	O

An	O
early	O
stand-alone	O
data	O
entry	O
machine	O
that	O
stored	O
data	O
on	O
magnetic	O
tape	O
for	O
computer	O
entry	O

An	O
earlier	O
name	O
for	O
the	O
low-	O
power	O
mode	O
in	O
Bluetooth	B-ORG
4	O
,	O
ULP	B-PER
is	O
also	O
used	O
to	O
describe	O
various	O
low-power	O
sensor	O
networks	O

An	O
established	O
relationship	O
between	O
a	O
user	O
and	O
a	O
computer	O
,	O
network	O
or	O
information	O
service	O

An	O
earlier	O
application	O
development	O
environment	O
for	O
Smalltalk	O
for	O
Windows	B-MISC
and	I-MISC
OS/2	O
from	O
the	O
now-defunct	O
ObjectShare	B-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
,	O
Sunnyvale	B-LOC
,	O
CA	B-LOC

An	O
open	O
source	O
video	O
codec	O
that	O
supersedes	O
VP9	O
and	O
is	O
expected	O
in	O
2015	O

An	O
ITU	B-LOC
standard	O
for	O
analog	O
modem	O
error	O
checking	O
that	O
uses	O
LAP-M	O
as	O
the	O
primary	O
protocol	O
and	O
provides	O
MNP	B-ORG
Classes	I-ORG
2	O
through	O
4	O
as	O
an	O
alternative	O
protocol	O
for	O
compatibility	O

An	O
innovative	O
video	O
production	O
and	O
editing	O
system	O
for	O
Windows	B-MISC
from	I-MISC
NewTek	B-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
,	O
San	B-LOC
Antonio	I-LOC
,	O
TX	B-LOC

An	O
airplane	O
's	O
travel	O
path	O

An	O
audio	O
compression	O
method	O
from	O
Microsoft	B-ORG

An	O
Internet-based	B-MISC
system	O
that	O
enables	O
an	O
individual	O
or	O
a	O
company	O
to	O
publish	O
itself	O
to	O
the	O
entire	O
world	O
,	O
except	O
to	O
countries	O
or	O
locations	O
that	O
prohibit	O
the	O
free	O
interchange	O
of	O
information	O

An	O
earlier	O
version	O
of	O
Windows	B-MISC
for	I-MISC
the	O
desktop	O

An	O
open	O
source	O
layout	O
engine	O
that	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
render	O
Web	O
pages	O
in	O
Apple	B-ORG
's	O
Safari	O
,	O
Google	B-ORG
's	O
Chrome	O
and	O
other	O
Web	O
browsers	O

An	O
XML-based	O
language	O
for	O
defining	O
business	O
processes	O
from	O
Microsoft	B-ORG

An	O
XML	O
markup	O
language	O
that	O
describes	O
how	O
an	O
XML	O
document	O
is	O
converted	O
into	O
another	O
XML	O
document	O
with	O
a	O
different	O
tag	O
structure	O
,	O
or	O
into	O
HTML	O
or	O
text	O

An	O
operational	O
mode	O
in	O
Intel	B-ORG
64	O
and	O
AMD64	B-PER
CPUs	I-PER
that	O
enables	O
32-bit	O
applications	O
to	O
each	O
use	O
up	O
to	O
4GB	O
of	O
RAM	B-ORG

An	O
IEEE	B-ORG
standard	O
for	O
link	O
layer	O
discovery	O
in	O
Ethernet	O
networks	O

An	O
IEEE	B-ORG
working	O
group	O
that	O
is	O
defining	O
methods	O
for	O
improved	O
Wi-Fi	B-MISC
management	O
Including	O
the	O
ability	O
to	O
lower	O
power	O
when	O
not	O
needed	O
and	O
redirect	O
packets	O
to	O
different	O
access	O
points	O
to	O
balance	O
the	O
traffic	O
load	O
